oh the size of my head uncle
my sky god
I had a hair transplant here in Türkiye
and today is the day to take off the bandage
we go on this
i
Need to change my face
today you laugh at me
tomorrow you'll have to put me up
Oh how are you
Are you okay
Do You Have a Bath
is there right
i Need to pee bro
bi
beş on dakika bekleyecez
çok iyi sonucu şu anda hiçbi sıkıntı yok
yarın maksimum olcak zaten sonra inmeye başlıyo
who was under anesthesia she ended up going down
and it's natural
this is on
Oh be kandıraşım ile daıtıyo ya sıvı daıtıyo
if i had a normal face i would look
wants 1 good news
will increase
now it feels like my head is getting anxious
it's coming here for the eye